Hi, in this lesson, I want to show you the poplar-arose templates and best practices from other developers.
Cursor has a specific rules page where you can find a lot of examples for different languages, for different domains, so I would say hundreds, different topics, yeah, you can use and a lot of rules.
So, you can use the left sidebar to do filtering by languages and for example, the tabs to do filtering by official rules, for example, it might be from Cursor, yeah, and for example, you can use the poplar filter to see the popular one, which is the most downloaded to use by other developers.
And you can say it to see, "Oh, you can also search, for example, by keywords", like VRG, for example, for example, not just, yeah, and you will find what you need.
So, this rules we can use as user rules, as project rules, as team rules, doesn't matter.
So, I will show you some examples, we will go through those files and he will understand them better.
For example, all, this is the TypeScript rules, the first I see, yeah, because this category is the first one, and below we see the Python and the next there, etc.
So, okay, let's open some official, a few officials and few popular, like this one, I don't know, this one, and let me rest well, my favorite one, I guess this one.
And I will show you one by one. So, at the top, like, you can see, kind of description, yeah, what is it, it's the good lines for writing, NHS application with the RPC template.
So, there is an overview, so here is, in rules, we provide a project structure, really explicitly, like, AIC, okay, this is the project structure, we use, we have some initialize rules, yeah, how we imported, how we initialize it, so we can also do same, if you have some strict rules, yeah, you can have how to create a router.
Like, you can even provide a code examples, yeah, in rules, so any either follows them. For example, this is how the client sites up.
But this rule is complex, it can work, if you work on really code base, where you have so strict rules and only like one pattern, each developer should follow, those, and you can use this example, yeah.
It's fine, but normally, if you follow the same pattern in other files, sort of view loop for the sibling files and we will read how you write the code and you'll write the code.
So, okay, another one is from super base, external database, you see, it says how critical instructions, so never generate something, you can also mention the rules, how to not do, yeah.
And how it's allowed to do, so you see requirements, so you must never use, you must never import, you must use, you must use only, you can also use this words.
Yeah, I normally reads them and understand, but sometimes he can also miss because he also did mistakes.
So, this is more 100% everything works, but normally you follow it good, yeah.
Okay, you see also the code examples right here.
And let's check something more close to the front end, like we have this one, yeah, at the top, we define the rule, EI, you're an expert in TypeScript.
Majes, najes, approtors, so we specify the technical stack, you work in on the EI, send key an expert in this domain, so we just specify the domain.
Then we can have a sections, like sections for code style, instructor for naming convention for TypeScript usage and you define the list of rules for each section, yeah.
You can also give some examples if you want.
So, the next one is kind of without the sections, yeah, we define the role of P.I.
I could say in your senior front end developer, expert in blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
Your thoughtful, give clear answers and brilliant and reasoning.
And then we just provide the list of construction, this is kind of a simplified version of rules when you don't.
You don't have some strict rules, yeah, you just want to write something good, yeah, you can start with just a list of rules rather than defining a sections.
Yeah, sections might work if you are experienced developers, you know exactly what you need, how you work, so then you can define a sections.
If you just start and you can just copy and use some basic stuff here from this rules, like just list of rules and then step by step, just add one rule to rules when you will understand, okay, I need this one.
Oh, yeah, I doing this, but I need to fix this and you can extend so you shouldn't have a big file, this rules at the beginning when you start, so it's adoption by time, so it's step by step process to extend it.
First, if you copy paste the whole guide, it might want to work for you, because some of rules you see different and then you will manually fix it after the ISO, the better is generated by yourself copying carefully adding all the lines one by one and test how it works for you.
So, the next one which I like, it's really detailed and follow a lot of best practices template, it's quite big, yeah, but it's what I like about it, that it has clear affections.
Like something generic, we write, we asked to write some clean, maintainable and scalable code, follow, select principles, refer functional and decorative programming, also what I like, we ask you, I first do planning, begin with step by step planning, write some detailed,
code before implementation, and we can check if I like the idea, if I like the implementation, yeah, this is kind of having a plan mode, yeah, with the eye.
And it's really can save you much tokens can save you time, because you will get some ideas from the eye, how it's going to implement it, and if you like it, you can build, if you don't, you can change the structure of the plan.
So, the next, this is kind of a yes lean or piloting here how indentions, indentation, you use code and then set for so you can normally configure it for here, or just in yes lean, just say I follow the yes intros.
So, what I like the name in conventions, because, for example, if that's the eye, okay, so, for example, if you write in the components, or type definitions, so interfaces,
this is use please podcast case, yeah, Pascal case, it's like this, a button from a capital letter.
For example, you use Bob case for directory names like this for file names, a comma case, you use for variables functions, and for example, for environment variables, or constants, you use upper case, it's really popular best practices, so, and they least it all here, so you can just, if you like them, you follow them, you can just go to paste.
And so, I think you will like them.
Also, the nice one is specific name and patterns about, like, it's also good practice for all handlers, like when you have a click, because a mid handler, add a prefix handle for variables, which is with verb, you can add a slot in has a or can submit.
So, like, for the hooks, you can use word use, never use short words, use the full complete words.
So, this has a lot of nice rules, you can definitely consider and copy, paste something for your rules.
It has best practices for next year, or several components, it has something important about TypeScript, UI styling, it has also rules about state management.
For example, if it's global state, what do you use for error handling, for testing, of course, it's often important, because if you write as you can spend a lot of time,
and if you have a really strict rules for writing tests, and you don't save much more time, and do it, I do it all.
At my job project, I have strict rules for writing unit tests, and it's really helpful.
So, of course, not always, but I spent less time, so they write it by myself.
I just take asking to fix it when it's needed. It also has some rules about security, some requirements, accessibility, etc.
So, it's really good set, I think we will use it in the next lesson.
Okay, I hope this lesson was useful for you, and you can search by all these rules, write to find something for you, that will work, and in the next lesson, I will show you how to apply them in course all.
Okay, see you in the next video.